

YHONATAN SMITH YLACCAÑA CORDOVA

963982343

Arequipa 9

"Responsible, Proactive and Self-taught"

yylaccana@unsa.edu.pe

I'm 22 years old, I'm a person focused on the activities that must be carried out, when I program I love to test my products (software) and find errors that I can correct or aspects that can be improved. I like to work in a team because it is easier to achieve the main objective. Personally, I am a jovial and respectful person with others and their opinions, I like to play sports like soccer, volleyball and basketball.

KNOWLEDGE

- Mastery in programming languages (Java, Python, SQL y NoSQL)
- Understanding of agile work models.

Español Inglés

Software: Latex, Excel, PowerPoint, Word, MongoDB, Oracle, MariaDB, Netbeans,

EDUCATION

2015 - 2017 Anta, Cusco

GRADUATED FROM COAR-CUSCO

Colegio de Alto Rendimiento Cusco

2018 - 2022 Arequipa, Arequipa STUDENT OF SYSTEMS ENGINEERING AT THE UNIVERSITY

Universidad Nacional de San Agustín

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2023 – April. 2023 Santo Tomas - Chumbivilcas

Municipality of Chumbivilcas

Job: Assistant of the System Engineering

- I controlled the SIGA and SIAF server.
- I design the webpage of the municipality.

Dec. 2019 – Feb. 2020 Arequipa, Arequipa

Public Transport Company COTUM S.A

Job: Controller of public transport vehicles on the Routes

- Using the company's software, I assigned public transport units to different routes.
- Using the information from the control points, evaluate the delays or overtaking of some drivers at the control points.

INTERESTS

- I would to work in a company and apply the knowledge acquired as well as learn more about it.
- Improve my domain of the English language and I would like to pass the Toelf exam
- I wanto to get more experience.